<?xml version="1.0"?>

<root available-locales="en_US" default-locale="en_US" version="1.0">
	<dynamic-element index-type="keyword" instance-id="vlhqnkbf" name="Title" type="text">
		<dynamic-content language-id="en_US"><![CDATA[Grab the best deals this June]]></dynamic-content>
	</dynamic-element>
	<dynamic-element index-type="text" instance-id="hmtfffzd" name="Header" type="text">
		<dynamic-content language-id="en_US"><![CDATA[We have a new offering related to some robots that we are introducing to the market. We want you to be our first beta tester!]]></dynamic-content>
	</dynamic-element>
	<dynamic-element index-type="keyword" instance-id="napiggij" name="Date" type="date">
		<dynamic-content language-id="en_US"><![CDATA[2021-06-02]]></dynamic-content>
	</dynamic-element>
	<dynamic-element index-type="text" instance-id="jkktxpvl" name="Photo" type="image">
		<dynamic-content language-id="en_US">
			<![CDATA[[$DOCUMENT_JSON:/site-initializer/documents/group/grab-the-best-deals-this-june.png$]]]>
		</dynamic-content>
	</dynamic-element>
	<dynamic-element index-type="keyword" instance-id="lmiocbyn" name="Text1u4b" type="text">
		<dynamic-content language-id="en_US"><![CDATA[Read More...]]></dynamic-content>
	</dynamic-element>
	<dynamic-element index-type="text" instance-id="htwpubko" name="Body" type="rich_text">
		<dynamic-content language-id="en_US"><![CDATA[<h3>MAKE UPDATES - FAST</h3>
<p>Plans change. But ActiNav lets you adapt quickly. Alter your workcell, bin size or place target in minutes, without changing other sections of the program.</p>
<p>It can be installed next to your existing machines, without changing your factory layout. And, once it's in, ActiNav can be shown how to run many kinds of parts in the same machine. Adding a new part type only takes a matter of hours, not weeks.</p>
<h3>DESIGNED TO FIT ANY WORKSPACE</h3>
<p>ActiNav has a habit of just… fitting in. It works with any type of gripper, from vacuum, to mechanical fingers, and magnetic. And it's compatible with many of our related UR+ accessories. On top of all this, it can remember an unlimited amount of pick and place positions.</p>
<p>ActiNav can also maneuver just fine in small spaces. So whatever your workstation looks like, there'll be a spot for it to call home.</p>
<p style="text-align:center"><img alt="" src="[$DOCUMENT_URL:/site-initializer/documents/group/actinav_square.png$]" /></p>
<p><br />
</p>
<h3>TRUSTED TO RUN UNATTENDED</h3>
<p>There's no need to monitor ActiNav once it gets to work. In fact, you can leave it for extended periods of time without having to check in.</p>
<p>This is because integrated path planning allows the technology to work inside large bins. The kind that don't need to be filled too often.&nbsp; When parts are running low, you'll be alerted, so production levels go up, along with your own productivity.</p>]]></dynamic-content>
	</dynamic-element>
	<dynamic-element index-type="keyword" instance-id="bowuodvp" name="Separator290u" type="separator" />
</root>